He Delivers.
The Transporter Refueled is a action, thriller, crime
film directed by Camille Delamarre.
The fast-paced action movie is again set in the criminal underworld in France, where Frank Martin is
known as The Transporter, because he is the best driver and mercenary money can buy.
In this installment, he meets Anna and they attempt to take down a group of ruthless
Russian human traffickers who also have kidnapped Frank’s father.
Frank Martin Jr., played by Ed Skrein.
Frank Martin Sr., played by Ray Stevenson.
Anna, played by Loan Chabanol.
Gina, played by Gabriella Wright.
Maria, played by Tatiana Pajković.
Qiao, played by Wenxia Yu.
The Transporter Refueled (French: Le Transporteur: Héritage; also known as Transporter 4) is a 2015 action
thriller film directed by Camille Delamarre and written by Bill Collage, Adam Cooper, and Luc Besson.
It serves as a reboot and the fourth film in the Transporter franchise.
It stars Ed Skrein as Frank Martin, alongside Ray Stevenson, Loan Chabanol, Gabriella Wright, Tatjana
Pajković, Yu Wenxia, Radivoje Bukvić, Lenn Kudrjawizki, Anatole Taubman, and Noémie Lenoir.
In the film, Frank finds himself caught up in a bank heist and
kidnapping plot orchestrated by Anna (Chabanol).
A fourth Transporter film was planned to feature original franchise star Jason Statham, who was
offered a three film deal with EuropaCorp to produce additional installments.
After negotiations with Statham fell through, Skrein was hired and the franchise was
rebooted, featuring no returning cast members from the first three films.
Principal photography took place in Paris.
The Transporter Refueled was theatrically released on 4 September 2015 in the United States and in France five
days later, by EuropaCorp; it is the first Transporter film primarily distributed by EuropaCorp.
The film received negative reviews from critics and
grossed $72.6 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of transporter, sequel,
french riviera, reboot, bank heist.
The tone is intense.